# **Shagun Parmar**

shagunparmar16@gmail.com 9879865724

## **Professional Summary -**

Carrying an extensive experience of 4 years across multiple domains, including Training & Development, Administrations, Business Development & Corporate Communications, Business Analytics, Virtual Events Organising and Management along with Overall Management and Growth of Organization.

**Skills:** Interpersonal Skills, Adaptable, Teamwork, End-to-End Coordination, Creativity & Designing, Time Management.

Microsoft Office Suite: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook.

Platforms: Onestream Live, Zoom, Hootsuite, Canva, Windows Video Editor, Format Factory,

Audacity.

## **Academic Qualifications:**

Bachelor of Business Administration, Navrachana University, Vadodara	2016
H.S.C, Convent of Jesus & Mary Girls High School, Vadodara	2013
S.S.C, Convent of Jesus & Mary Girls High School, Vadodara	2011

#### **Work Experience**

## <u>Associate Director - TiE Vadodara Forum</u>

March 2021 - Present

TiE Global - Vadodara Chapter is a non-profit organization launched in Feb 2021, devoted to fostering entrepreneurs and start-up eco-system across all Industries with its unwavering support at all levels from Incubation to throughout the entrepreneurial lifecycle. With a global reach and a local focus, the heart of TiE efforts lies in its five foundational programs — Mentoring, Networking, Education, Funding, and Incubation.

# Roles and Responsibilities:

- End to end membership management, start-up on boarding.
- Problem solving, handling queries, maintaining all relevant data.
- Building relationships with members, potential members, industry professionals and journalists.
- Managing the official social media accounts of TiE Vadodara, creating content for regular posts, creation of promotional materials for all events and forum, posting and promotion of on all social media channels, responding to the queries and comments raised.
- Overseeing the regular updates on the website
- Planning, organising, managing, and executing events supporting the upliftment of start-up/ entrepreneurial community.
- Managing and oversee the project end-to-end.

- Program planning, execution, coordination, marketing keeping track of program data and cohort information, and creating reports.
- Generating leads, organizing speaker sessions, managing workshops, coordination and launching new programs, creating marketing strategies to reach out the target audience, selecting right speaker for right session.
- Implement and ensure the successful delivery of the program, including optimizing start-up engagement and measuring start-up satisfaction
- Assist on all program prep and execution

#### **Communication & Business Development- Unified Growth Foundation**

May 2019 – Present

Unified Growth Foundation is a multi-disciplinary consultant and technocrats' group with fortes in various domains as we have a team of Subject Matter Experts and Advisors. Each member of the professional team has a rigorous practice in one's pitch of proficiency and a track record of accomplishment in national/international ventures. This creates the substratum of success in providing management and technical solutions to a broad spectrum of our clients

## Roles and Responsibilities:

- Coordination and communication with various university managements as well as students for various international educational programs exclusively designed for university students.
- Prepared and maintained written communications, reports, and documents to ensure smooth operations.
- Counselled and followed-up with the prospective student candidates for international educational programs.
- Acting as a mediator between third party vender, university management and students to provide them a smooth support system for all processes pertaining to International Desk.
- Supported the initial screening and first-hand assessment for in-house recruitment of various roles.
- Conducted research, gathered information for various projects to support with potential network.
- Gathered requirements for ongoing projects and organized details for management use.
- Maintained project schedules by managing timelines and making proactive adjustments.
- Coordination and Support virtual events such as Vadodara Marathon, Dance pe Change (NewYork Project) and many such projects.
- Coordination with the technical team for company website along with the quality check of the same.

An Indian multinational pharmaceutical company, that manufactures and sells pharmaceutical formulations and active pharmaceutical ingredients (APIs) primarily in India and the United States.

#### Roles and Responsibilities:

- To support the Head of Learning & Development in the effective delivery of the overall L&D strategy.
- Creating training programmes that are aligned with the organization's objectives.
- Acting as the go to within the business for anyone with questions or queries regarding training and development plans.
- To record, collate and retain management information to demonstrate progress against KPIs and departmental goals and objectives.
- To contribute to L&D communications using a variety of mediums, mail, Intranet, paper etc.
- Responsible for overall administration and facility management.
- Involved in establishment of infrastructure related requirement of the academy.
- Acting as info-hub for providing administration related information and supervising administrative activities like general admin, verification of stationery stock and courier.
- Event Management, organizing meetings, conferences, making travel arrangements and hotel reservations for guests & foreign delegates.
- Independently handling accommodation and local travelling arrangements for participants.
- Setting up new automation systems in the Academy
- Overall training course administration starting from announcement to certification.

#### <u>Associate Research Analyst - Investis Digital</u>

July 2016 - July 2017

Investis Digital has been at the forefront of digital communications and marketing for two decades working with nearly 1,600 public companies in over 30 countries

## Roles and Responsibilities:

- Analyse the corporate websites according to various standards.
- Responsible for categorizing the company sector as per the set standard.
- Solving the clients query and providing customize analysis report as pet the request.
- Prioritizing the data using given keywords and assign the same to team member.
- Provide solutions / inputs which can help the team to enhance work efficiency.

## **Internship:**

#### **Zydex Industries**

#### **Duration of Work:** 02 Month (May 2015)

#### Roles and Responsibilities:

- Coordinated attendance management system and performance management system (PMS) through active observation and verbal instructions.
- Learned practical implications and operation of HR Intranet and COSEC which are the software interfaces used by the organization for different tasks.
- Executed desk procedure of new joiners and filing of Form 16 as well as PF nominees.

#### The Bluebird Foundation

#### **Duration of Work:** 01 Month (May 2014)

## **Roles and Responsibilities:**

- Seeking potential help-work for society.
- Sell hand-made books and paper bags.
- Prepare Event Flow of all the festivals in a Calendar Year.
- Noting Corporate Social Responsibility Activities of various Companies.

## **Additional Accomplishments:**

- Communications Training Program organized by NASSCOM
- Corporate Internship at Zydex Industries
- Industrial Visit and Study of Anand Milk Union Limited (Amul) and Piramal Glass Limited.
- Social Internship at The Bluebird Foundation
- Organizing of University Events: CSR, Annual gathering, Annual Magazine Launch, and other monthly events of the University.
- Active participation in organising Vadodara International Half Marathon
- "Joint Seminar on Partners in Growth New Business Ventures" held at ICAI Bhawan, Baroda.

Date:	
-------	--

Place: Vadodara. Shagun Parmar